Inventory of the National Cattlemen’s Association records, 1898-2018
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Committee Files, Series IV.
  - Tax and Credit committee - mailing, 1998 (Box 702)
- Affiliate Files, Series V.
  This series contains files concerning member associations of the NCA. It consists chiefly of correspondence, but also includes press releases, reports, and resolutions.
  - Adams County Cattlemen’s Association, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Affiliated Association Directories, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Affiliated Association, undated (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Affiliates, 1984-1986 (Box 125, Folders 4-9)
  - Alabama Cattlemen’s Association, 1953-1968 (Box 125, Folders 10-11)
  - Alabama Cattlemen’s Association, 1952-1969, 1980-1987, undated (Box 126, Folders 1-10)
  - Alaska Stock Growers Association, 1963-1965, 1967-1969 (Box 126, Folders 11-14)
  - Amador, El Dorado, Sacramento, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - American Aberdeen Angus Breeders Association, 1955 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - American Angus Association, 1958-1969, 1988 (Box 127, Folders 1-3)
  - American Brahman Breeders Association, 1955-1969 (Box 127, Folders 4-5)
  - American Brahman Breeders, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - American Charolaise Breeders Association, 1956 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - American Galloway Breeders Association, 1968 (Box 127, Folders 8-9)
  - American Guernsey Cattle Club, 1958-1963 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - American Hereford Association, 1955-1969 (Box 127, Folders 11-13)
  - American International Charolais Association, 1961-1969, 1981, 1985 (Box 127, Folders 14-19)
  - American Jersey Cattle Club, 1958-1963 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - American Polled Hereford Association, 1962-1968, 1985 (Box 127, Folders 21-22)
  - American Scotch Highland Breeders Association, 1958-1969 (Box 127, Folder 23)
  - American Shorthorn Breeders Association, 1958-1968 (Box 127, Folder 24)
  - American Simmental Association, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 25)
  - Arizona Cattle Feeders Association, 1958-1967, undated (Box 127, Folders 26-28)
  - Arizona Cattle Feeders Association, 1963-1969, 1987-1988 (Box 128, Folders 1-5)
  - Arizona Cattle Growers Association, Biography Roderick J. McMullin, 1957 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Arizona Cattle Growers Association, 1956-1961, 1964-1967 (Box 128, Folders 7-12)
  - Arizona Cattle Growers Association, 1960, 1962-1969, 1985-1988 (Box 129, Folders 1-9)
  - Arizona Hereford Association, 1958 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Arizona Wool Growers’ Association, 1959 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Arkansas Cattlemen’s Association, 1953-1969, 1986-1987, undated (Box 129, Folders 12-18)
  - Arkansas Valley Stock Feeders’ Association, 1959, 1961 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Ayrshire Breeders Association, 1958-1960 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Baker County Livestock Association, 1961 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Beartooth Livestock Association, 1962 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Beaver Creek Stock Association, 1961-1962 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Bent-Prowers Cattle and Horse Growers Association, 1961-1969 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Blackfoot Valley Stockmen’s Association, 1957-1962 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Blue Stem Cattlemen’s Association, 1959, 1961 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Blue Valley Stockgrowers Association, 1959, 1961 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Boulder-South Larimer Stockmen’s Association, 1961, 1963 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Breed Associations, 1953, undated (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Brown Swiss Cattle Breeders’ Association, 1958-1960 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Calcasieu Parish Cattlemen’s Association, 1959-1962 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - California Beef Industry Council, 1954-1956, undated (Box 130, Folders 14-19)
  - California Cattle Feeders Association, 1955-1969, 1981 (Box 130, Folders 20-24)
  - California Cattlemen’s Association, 1963-1967 (Box 130, Folder 25)
  - California Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1963 (Box 131, Folders 1-7)
  - California Cattlemen’s Association, 1947-1969, 1981-1985 (Box 132, Folders 1-11)
  - California Cattlemen’s Association, 1955, 1960-1968 (Box 133, Folders 1-5)
  - California Hereford Association, 1959-1961 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - California Wool Growers Association, 1958-1964 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Carter County Sheep and Cattle Growers Association, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Cattlemen’s Association of Morgan and Associated Counties, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Central Arizona Cattle Feeders’ Association, 1955 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Central Fremont Cattle and Horse Association, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Central Livestock Association, 1966-1967 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Certified Livestock Markets Association, 1966-1967 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Chaffee County Cattlemen’s Association, 1961-1962 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Chelan County Cattlemen’s Association, 1964 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Coastal Cattle Association Inc., 1959, 1961 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Colorado Association of Soil Conservation Districts, 1960-1961 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Colorado Cattle Feeders Association, 1957-1969, 1981-1987 (Box 133, Folders 18-22)
  - Colorado Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1959, 1962-1969, undated (Box 133, Folders 23-25)
  - Colorado Cattlemen’s Association, 1957-1958, 1960-1969, 1980-1988 (Box 134, Folders 1-14)
  - Colorado Hereford Association, 1959 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Colorado Stock Growers and Feeders Association, 1947 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Commercial Cattle Company of Arizona, 1963 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Cowbelles, 1954-1980 (Box 134, Folders 18-19)
  - Cowbelles, 1955-1958 (Box 135, Folders 1-7)
  - Cowbelles, 1958-1963, 1965-1981 (Box 136, Folders 1-6)
  - Cowbelles, Lifetime Membership, Lyman, Mrs. O.W., 1964 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Cowbelles, Mary Louise Lyman Graduate Fellowship-Kruchek, Susan Joy, 1969-1970 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Cowbelles, 1955-1980 (Box 136, Folders 9-14)
  - Cowbelles, Beef for Father’s Day, 1954-1959, undated (Box 136, Folders 15-19)
  - Cowbelles, Beef for Father’s Day, 1955-1960, undated (Box 137, Folders 1-6)
  - Cowbelles, Cook Book, 1953-1956, undated (Box 137, Folders 7-12)
  - Crook County Stockgrowers Association, 1956-1964 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Douglas County Cattle Association, 1957-1959 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Easters Pennington County Grazing District, 1960 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Elbert County Livestock Association, 1955-1962 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Ferry County Livestock Association, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Florida Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1968 (Box 137, Folders 18-20)
  - Florida Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1969, 1981-1988 (Box 138, Folders 1-9)
  - Fort Collins Lamb Feeders Association, 1959, 1962 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Fremont County Stockgrowers Association, 1958-1968 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Frying Pan Stock Growers Association, 1958 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Georgia Cattlemen’s Association, 1968-1969, 1985, 1989 (Box 138, Folders 13-14)
  - Georgia Livestock Association, 1955-1958, 1960-1967 (Box 138, Folders 15-17)
  - Georgia Livestock Association, 1963-1968, undated (Box 139, Folders 1-5)
  - Gila County Cattle Growers Association, 1955-1962 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Gilpin-Jefferson Livestock Association, 1962, 1968 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Glasgow Muir Valley Livestock Association, 1962 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Grand Mesa Livestock Association, 1957-1958 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Greater North Dakota Association, 1957, 1961 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Green River Valley Association, 1964 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Gunnison County Stockgrowers Association, 1959-1969 (Box 139, Folders 12-13)
  - Hawaii Cattlemen’s Council, 1958-1968 (Box 139, Folders 14-19)
  - Highland Hereford Breeders Association, 1959-1962 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Holstein-Friesian Association of America, 1959-1965 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Idaho Cattle Association, 1985 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Idaho Cattle Feeders Association, 1961-1969, 1980, undated (Box 140, Folders 4-10)
  - Idaho Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1968, 1980-1987 (Box 140, Folders 11-20)
  - Idaho Cattlemen’s Association, 1952-1967 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Beef Association, 1986 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Cattlemen’s Association, undated (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Illinois Beef Association, 1985, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Illinois Cattlemen’s Association, 1964-1969 (Box 141, Folders 5-7)
  - Indiana Beef Cattle Association, 1985-1987 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Indiana Cattlemen’s Association, 1966-1969 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Indiana Beef Cattle Association, 1980-1981 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - International Beef Breeders, 1968 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - International Brangus Breeders Association, 1964-1969, 1986 (Box 141, Folders 12-13)
  - Inyo County Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1963 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - Iowa Beef Producers Association, 1966-1969 (Box 141, Folders 15-18)
  - Iowa Cattlemen’s Association, 1980-1988 (Box 141, Folder 19)
  - Iowa Livestock Feeders, 1960 (Box 141, Folder 20)
  - Jefferson Davis Parish Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1962 (Box 141, Folder 21)
  - Junior American National Cattlemen Association, 1956-1958 (Box 141, Folders 22-24)
  - Junior American National Cattlemen Association, 1957-1969 (Box 142, Folders 1-5)
  - Junior American National Cattlemen Association (JANCA), 1957-1972 (Box 686, Folders 12)
  - Kansas Livestock Association, 1950-1969, 1980-1988 (Box 142, Folders 6-13)
  - Kansas Livestock Association, 1952-1968 (Box 143, Folders 1-2)
  - Kentucky Beef Cattle Association, 1985-1986 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky Cattlemen’s Association, 1959-1969 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - King County Cattlemen’s Association, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Kittitas County Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1968 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Klickatat County Livestock Growers, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - La Plata County Cattlemen’s Association, 1968 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Larimer County Stockgrowers Association, 1961-1962 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Lawrence, Green, and Texas Counties, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln County Stockmen’s Association, 1959-1968 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Louisiana Cattlemen’s Association, 1954-1969, 1985 (Box 143, Folders 12-18)
  - Mancos Cattlemen’s Association, 1961-1962 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Marfa Production Credit Association, 1968 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Marshall Feeder Cattle Association, 1969 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Maryland Aberdeen Angus Association, 1959 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Maryland Beef Cattle Producers, 1956-1969 (Box 144, Folders 5-7)
  - Michigan Beef Cattle Breeders Association, 1959, 1961 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Michigan Cattle Feeders Association, 1961 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Michigan Cattlemen’s Association, 1980-1988 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Minnesota Cattlemen’s Association, 1968 (Box 144, Folders 11-16)
  - Minnesota State Cattlemen’s Association, 1980-1987 (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - Mississippi Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1959, 1964 (Box 144, Folders 18-19)
  - Mississippi Cattlemen’s Association, 1960-1969, 1980-1986, undated (Box 145, Folders 1-8)
  - Missoula Hereford Association, 1957-1961 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Missouri Cattlemen’s Convention, 1985-1988 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Missouri Livestock Association, 1959-1969 (Box 145, Folders 11-13)
  - Missouri Livestock Feeders, 1981 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Modoc County Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1962 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Moffat County Cattle Association, 1969 (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - Mohave County Livestock Growers Association, 1958-1961 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - Montana-Local Associations, 1961 (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Montana-Local Associations, 1961-1962, undated (Box 146, Folders 1-2)
  - Montana Association of Grazing Districts, 1963 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Montana Cattle Feeders Association, 1962 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Montana Stock Growers Association, 1955-1969, undated (Box 146, Folders 5-12)
  - Montana Stock Growers Association, 1963-1965, 1967-1968 (Box 147, Folders 1-8)
  - Montana Stock Growers Association, 1956-1969, 1981-1988, undated (Box 148, Folders 1-6)
  - Monterey County Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1963 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Morgan County Cattlemen’s Association, 1964 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Mount Adams Cattle Association, 1958 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - Mount Whitney Livestock Association, 1955-1961 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Musselshell Valley Stock Growers Association, 1960-1962 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Nebraska Livestock Feeders Association, 1988 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Nebraska Stock Growers Association, 1955-1967 (Box 148, Folders 13-16)
  - Nebraska Stock Growers Association, 1946-1969, 1981-1988 (Box 149, Folders 1-5)
  - Nevada Cattlemen’s Association, 1980-1987 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Nevada State Cattle Association, 1950, 1955-1969 (Box 149, Folders 7-14)
  - Nevada State Cattle Association, 1963-1967 (Box 150, Folders 1-2)
  - Nevada Wool Growers Association, 1958-1962 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - New Mexico Cattle Growers Association, 1954-1967 (Box 150, Folders 4-10)
  - New Mexico Cattle Growers Association, 1948-1969, 1981-1987, undated (Box 151, Folders 1-5)
  - New Mexico Wool Growers Association, 1958-1963 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - New York Beef Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1969, 1985-1986, undated (Box 151, Folders 7-11)
  - Niobrara Forest Users Association, 1955, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - North American Limousin Foundation, 1969, 1986 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - North Carolina Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1969, 1980-1985, undated (Box 151, Folders 14-16)
  - North Carolina Livestock Association, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - North Dakota Grazing Association, 1961-1962 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - North Dakota Stockmen’s Association, 1955-1959 (Box 151, Folders 19-20)
  - North Dakota Stockmen’s Association, 1952-1988 (Box 152, Folders 1-5)
  - North East Panhandle Feeders Association, 1957 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - North Park Stock Growers Association, 1958-1969 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - North Phillips County Co-Operative, 1960-1961 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Northeastern Colorado Cattlemen’s Association, 1966-1963 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Northeastern New Mexico Livestock Association, 1962 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Northern Arizona Cattlemen’s Association, 1961 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Northern Indiana Hereford Association, 1959 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Northern New Mexico Livestock Association, 1958-1965 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Northwest Oklahoma Cattlemen’s Association, 1960 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Ohio Cattle Feeders Association, 1964-1969 (Box 152, Folders 15-17)
  - Ohio Valley Charolais Association, Inc., 1967 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Okanogan County Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1968 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Oklahoma Cattlemen’s Association, Bill-H.R. 4375, 1965 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Oklahoma Cattlemen’s Association, 1954-1969, 1987-1988 (Box 153, Folders 2-13)
  - Oregon Cattlemen’s Association, 1961-1968 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Oregon Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1967 (Box 154, Folders 1-7)
  - Oregon Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1969, 1980-1988, undated (Box 155, Folders 1-9)
  - Oregon Wool Growers’ Association, 1959-1963 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Ouray County, Colorado Cattlemen, Ridgeway, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Owyhee Cattlemen’s Association, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Pan American Charolais Association, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - Panhandle Livestock Association, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - Panola County Cattlemen’s Association, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - Panola-Tate Livestock Association, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - Pend-Oreille County Livestock Association, 1959-1962 (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvania Cattlemen’s Association, 1985-1986 (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Pikes Peak Cattlemen’s Association, 1955-1961 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - Pony of the Americas Club, 1961-1963 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - Pueblo County Stockmen’s Association, 1958-1959 (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - Ragged Mountain Livestock Association, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - Red Angus Association of America, 1964-1986 (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - Red Poll Beef Breeders International, 1968-1969 (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - Rio Blanco Stock Growers Association, 1959-1969 (Box 155, Folders 25-26)
  - Routt County Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1968 (Box 155, Folder 27)
  - Ruby Valley Stock Association, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - San Diego County Hereford Breeders Association, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - San Luis Valley Cattlemen’s Association, 1957-1961 (Box 155, Folder 30)
  - Sandhills Feeder Cattle Association, 1946 (Box 155, Folder 31)
  - Sandhills Cattle Association, 1955-1962 (Box 155, Folder 32)
  - Santa Clara County Cattlemen’s Association, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - Santa Gertrudis Breeders International, 1955-1985 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Siskiyou County Cattlemen’s Association, 1963 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - South Carolina Cattlemen’s Association, 1964-1968, 1980, 1985 (Box 156, Folders 3-4)
  - South Carolina Livestock Producers Association, 1961-1963 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - South Dakota Livestock Association, 1981-1987 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - South Dakota Stock Growers Association, 1955-1969, 1981-1988 (Box 156, Folders 7-16)
  - South Dakota Stock Growers Association, 1952-1969, undated (Box 157, Folders 1-4)
  - Southeast Kansas Hereford Association, 1959 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Southeastern Montana Stock Growers Association, 1955, 1961 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Southern Colorado Livestock Association, 1958, 1961 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Southwestern Colorado Livestock Association, 1958, 1961 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Southwestern Simmental-Simbrah Meeting, Benedict Ranch, 1986 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Square Top Cattle and Horse Association, 1958, 1961 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - State Associations, 1955-1958, 1961, undated (Box 157, Folders 11-15)
  - State Association Magazines, Questionnaires, 1960-1961 (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - State Presidents and Secretaries, 1959-1960 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Stevens County Livestock Association, 1958 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - T-Bone Club, 1955-1968 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Tennessee Cattlemen’s Association, 1986 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Tennessee Livestock Association, 1954-1965 (Box 157, Folders 21-22)
  - Tennessee Livestock Association, 1956-1969, undated (Box 158, Folders 1-4)
  - Texas and Southwestern Cattle Raisers Association, 1955-1968, undated (Box 158, Folders 5-11)
  - Texas and Southwestern Cattle Feeders Association, 1967 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Texas and Southwestern Cattle Feeders Association, 1967 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Texas and Southwestern Cattle Raisers Association, 1959-1969, 1981-1988 (Box 159, Folders 2-10)
  - Texas Brahman Association, 1981 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Texas Cattle Feeders Association, 1968-1969, 1985-1988, undated (Box 159, Folders 12-15)
  - Texas Hereford Association, 1959, 1961 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Tri-State Livestock Credit Corporation, 1963 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - Uintah Cattle and Horse Association, 1955, 1957 (Box 159, Folder 18)
  - Umatilla County Cattlemen’s Association, 1959 (Box 159, Folder 19)
  - Upper Green River Cattle Association, 1958-1959 (Box 159, Folder 20)
  - Utah Cattle and Horse Growers Association, 1954-1956 (Box 159, Folders 21-23)
  - Utah Cattlemen’s Association, 1963-1967 (Box 159, Folder 24)
  - Utah Cattlemen’s Association, 1956-1969, 1985, 1987 (Box 160, Folders 1-7)
  - Virginia Beef Cattle Association, 1960-1969 (Box 160, Folders 8-10)
  - Virginia Beef Cattle Producers Association, 1956-1960 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Beef Cattlemen’s Association, 1961-1964 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Cattlemen’s Association, 1987 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Wallowa County Stock Growers, 1955-1962 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Washington Cattle Feeders Association, 1960-1969, 1980 (Box 160, Folders 15-17)
  - Washington Cattle Feeders Association, 1964 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Washington Cattlemen’s Association, 1956-1965, 1967-1969, 1980-1988, undated (Box 161, Folders 2-15)
  - Washington County Cattlemen’s Association, 1964 (Box 161, Folder 16)
  - Weld County Cattlemen’s Association, 1986-1987 (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - West Texas Hereford Association, 1959 (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - West Virginia Cattlemen’s Association, 1986 (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - West Virginia Hereford Breeders Association, 1958 (Box 161, Folder 20)
  - Western Nebraska Hereford Association, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 21)
  - Western Pine Association, 1947-1948, 1954 (Box 161, Folders 22-23)
  - Western South Dakota Sheep Growers Association, 1963 (Box 161, Folder 24)
  - Whatcom County Cattlemen’s Association, 1964 (Box 161, Folder 25)
  - Whitman County Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1959 (Box 161, Folder 26)
  - Williamson County Livestock Association, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 27)
  - Willow Creek Co-Op State Grazing District, 1961 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Wisconsin Cattlemen’s Association, 1981-1987 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Wyoming Cowbelles, 1961 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Wyoming Stock Growers Association, 1946, 1952-1969, 1981-1988 (Box 162, Folders 4-17)
  - Yakima County Cattlemen’s Association, 1958-1963 (Box 162, Folder 18)
  - Affiliated Association of Executive Officers, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Alabama Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971, 1974-1975 (Box 163, Folders 2-5)
  - Alaska Stock Growers Association, 1966 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - American Angus, 1967, 1970, 1973 (Box 163, Folders 7-9)
  - American Brahman Breeders, 1967, 1971 (Box 163, Folders 10-11)
  - American Charolais, 1971-1972 (Box 163, Folders 12-13)
  - American Hereford, 1967, 1971, 1973 (Box 163, Folders 14-16)
  - American Polled Hereford, 1971-1972 (Box 163, Folders 17-18)
  - American Scotch Highland, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - American Shorthorn, 1967, 1971-1972 (Box 163, Folders 20-22)
  - American Simmental, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 23)
  - Arizona Cattle Feeders Association, 1966, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 163, Folders 24-27)
  - Arizona Cattle Growers Association, 1966, 1971, 1973, 1975 (Box 163, Folders 28-31)
  - Arkansas Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971-1972, 1975 (Box 163, Folders 32-35)
  - Brangus, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 36)
  - California Cattle Feeders Association, 1966, 1971, 1973 (Box 163, Folders 37-39)
  - California Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971, 1973 (Box 163, Folders 40-42)
  - Colorado Cattle Feeders Association, 1966, 1971-1972, 1975 (Box 163, Folders 43-46)
  - Colorado Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971, 1973, 1975 (Box 164, Folders 1-4)
  - Florida Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971, 1973, 1975 (Box 164, Folders 5-8)
  - General Membership, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 164, Folders 9-36)
    Various states (Alabama-Wyoming)
  - Georgia Livestock Association, 1966, 1971 (Box 164, Folders 37-38)
  - Georgia Cattlemen’s Association, 1972, 1975 (Box 164, Folders 39-40)
  - Hawaii Cattlemen’s Council, Inc., 1966, 1973 (Box 164, Folders 41-42)
  - Idaho Cattle Feeders Association, 1966, 1971-1972, 1975 (Box 164, Folders 43-46)
  - Idaho Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971, 1973, 1975 (Box 164, Folders 47-50)
  - Illinois, 1971 (Box 164, Folder 51)
  - Indiana Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971, 1973 (Box 164, Folders 52-54)
  - International Beef Breeders, 1967 (Box 165, Folders 1-2)
  - International Charolais, 1967 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Maine Anjou, 1973 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Iowa Beef Producers, 1966, 1971 (Box 165, Folders 5-6)
  - Iowa Cattlemen’s Association, 1975 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Kansas Livestock Association, 1966, 1971 (Box 165, Folders 8-9)
  - Iowa Cattlemen’s Association, 1973 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Kansas Livestock Association, 1972, 1975 (Box 165, Folders 11-12)
  - Kentucky Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971-1972 (Box 165, Folders 13-15)
  - Louisiana Cattlemen’s Association, 1966, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 165, Folders 16-19)
  - Maryland Beef Cattle Producers, 1966, 1971, 1973 (Box 165, Folders 20-22)
  - Minnesota, 1972 (Box 165, Folder 23)
  - Minnesota Beef Producers Association, 1974 (Box 165, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Associations, 1967, 1971-1972 (Box 165, Folders 25-27)
  - Miscellaneous Breed Associations, 1970-1974 (Box 165, Folder 28)